Guide to the Jobs With Justice Records 2001-2012
Jobs With Justice Records
- D3: Treston Davis Faulkner Files: Field Work and Campus Work (Box 16)
  - Chicago JWJ, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - National Student Congress, 2000-2001 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Treston Faulkner's Congress 2G Materials, 1999-2000 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - USSA News, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    March 13 2002
  - Workshop Outlines (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Workshop Originals, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Manual (Box 16, Folder 10)
    Contains two CD's
  - Anti-Oppression Resources, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    October 6 2004
  - Anti-Oppression Resources (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - 55th National Student Congress, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Student-Labor Roundtable Materials, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Student Labor Pre-Conference, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Student Labor Pre-Conference 2000 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Student Labor Pre-Conference 1999 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Notes, SEJAC 2009 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Communication with Major Gregory, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Workshop and Useful Rules, 2008-2010 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Travel, 2008-2010 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Local Students Contacts and Lists (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - "Grow" News, 2001-2002 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - General "Grow" Documents, 1998-2000 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Student-Labor GROW Originals, 2000-2001 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - NSLA GROW, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    November 2 - 5 2000
  - New GROW Materials, 1997-1998 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Labor GROW, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - GROW Strategy Charts, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - GROW 2001 Evaluations (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Complete NSLA GROW Packet, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Useful Professional Development Worksheets, 2008-2010 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Local SIAP Development, 2008-2010 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Strategic Planning, 2008-2010 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Anti-Oppression Articles, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - SLAP Presentations to JWJ Planning Committee, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - General Documents (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - 2001 SLACtivist news (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Worker Quotes (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - GROW and SLAP Monthly Reports, 2000-2002 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - List of Useful Acronyms (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Useful Spanish Words and Phrases (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - ARAW Article 2, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 43)
    Tuesday, December 14 2004
  - ARAW Articles, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 44)
    February 24 2005
  - Campaign Filled Out GROW (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - SLAP Internal Documents, 2001-2002 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - SLAP Hiring, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Reimbursement and Check Request Copies, 2006-2007 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Student-Worker Workshop Handouts (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Direct Action handouts (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Reimbursements and Receipts, 2006-2007 (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Credit Card Statement Copies, 2005-2006 (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - CC Receipts Originals, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Credit Card Receipts, 2005-2006 (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - Staff meeting Notes and Materials, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - Staff Meeting Notes and Materials, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - Fast Track 2001 (Box 16, Folder 57)
- E1: Local Coalitions 1992-2003 (Box 17)
  - Albany NY Solidarity Committee, Solidarity Notes, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Albany Solidarity Committee Solidarity Notes, 1993-1997 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Albany NY Solidarity Committee of the Capital District, 1995-1997 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Massachusetts JWJ Workers Rights Boards, 1995-1996 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Massachusetts Workers Rights, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Buffalo Workers' Rights Board, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Buffalo NY, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Buffalo NY Coalition for Economic Justice, Workers' Rights Board, 1995-1996 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Buffalo New York Jobs with Justice, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Buffalo, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Buffalo New York Coalition for Economic Justice, 1993-1999 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - New York City, Workers' Rights Board, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - New York City Jobs with Justice Workers Rights Board, 1995-1999 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - New York City Jobs with Justice, 1995-1996 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - New York City Jobs with Justice, 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - New York City Jobs with Justice, 1991-1992 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - New York, 2001-2003 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - New York City Jobs with Justice, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Consumer Coalition for Quality Healthcare, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Jobs with Justice Documents, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Healthcare, New York Jobs with Justice, 1992-1995 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Long Island, 2000-2001 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Long Island Jobs with Justice, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - New York City Jobs with Justice, 2000-2001 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - New York City Workers' Rights Board, 2000-2001 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Newsday Articles, New York Jobs with Justice Hearing, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    October 30 2001
  - New York City, New York, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - New York City Jobs with Justice, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Syracuse Jobs with Justice, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Syracuse, New York, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Jobs with Justice, new Zealand, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Cleveland, Ohio Continued, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Cleveland, Ohio, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Jobs with Justice Documents, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Cleveland Jobs with Justice, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 35)
- E2: Local Coalitions 1992-2003 (Box 18)
  - Cleveland, Ohio Jobs with Justice, 1994-2002 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Cleveland JWJ Workers Rights Board, 1994-2000 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Cleveland Jobs with Justice, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Cleveland Planning Retreat, 2000-2001 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Cleveland Workers' Rights Boards, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Cleveland, Ohio, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Cleveland Jobs with Justice, 1999-2000 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Portland, 2002-2003 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Rhode Island Jobs with Justice, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Rhode Island Jobs with Justice, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Rhode Island Jobs with Justice, 1996-2000 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Boston J4J Campaign, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Providence, Rhode Island, 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Youngstown, Ohio Jobs with Justice Possible, 1996-2001 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Lorain Jobs with Justice, 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Columbiana, Ohio, 1994-1999 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Columbiana Jobs with Justice, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Cleveland Jobs with Justice, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Cleveland, 2001-2003 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Columbiana, Ohio, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Cleveland, Ohio, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Mahoning Valley, 1992-2003 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Tri-Mahoning Valley Jobs with Justice, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Columbus and Cleveland, Ohio, 2001-2006 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Kentucky Economic Justice Training, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    March 1997
  - St. Louis, Missouri, 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Protest Corporate Globalization and Announce Kentucky-Mexico Worker Exchange (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Labor Forum on Merger, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Puerto Rico, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - St. Louis Jobs with Justice, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - St. Louis, 2002-2003 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - St. Louis, Missouri, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - St. Louis, Missouri Jobs with Justice, 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Detroit, 2001-2003 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Detroit Workers' Rights Board, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Detroit, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Detroit, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Kalamazoo, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Michigan Jobs with Justice, 1993-2001 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Mississippi South Central Labor Union, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Montana, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Montana, 1996-1999 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Omaha, Nebraska, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Missoula, Montana, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Montana Community Labor Alliance, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Montana Community Labor Alliance "I'll Be There", 1995-1998 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Missoula, Montana, 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 47)
- E3: Local Coalitions 1992-2003 (Box 19)
  - Montana Community-Labor Alliance, 1994-1997 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Louisville, Kentucky, 1997-1998 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Louisville, Kentucky, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Louisville, Kentucky Jobs with Justice, 1997-1998 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Louisville, Kentucky Jobs with Justice, 1992-1997 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Louisville-Tyson Strike, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - JwJ Documents, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Louisville, Kentucky Jobs with Justice, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Kentucky Jobs with Justice, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Kentucky, 2001-2003 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Boston, Massachusetts, 1997-1998 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Boston, Massachusetts, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Massachusetts Jobs with Justice, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Massachusetts Jobs with Justice, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Miscellanseous Massachusetts Documents, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Massachusetts Jobs with Justice, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Massachusetts Jobs with Justice, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Boston, Massachusetts, 2002-2003 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Massachusetts Jobs with Justice, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Boston Jobs with Justice, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Massachusetts Jobs with Justice, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Boston Planning Retreat, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Massachusetts-Merrimack Valley Jobs with Justice, 2001-2002 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Western Massachusetts, 2002-2003 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- E4: Local Coalitions 1992-2003 (Box 20)
  - Western Massachusetts Jobs with Justice, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Western Massachusetts Jobs with Justice, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Western Massachusetts, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Western Massachusetts, 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Western Massachusetts Jobs with Justice Workers Rights Board, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Western Massachusetts Jobs with Justice, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Boston, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Boston Right to Organize, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Boston, Workers' Rights Board, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Massachusetts Jobs with Justice, 1997-1999 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - North Carolina Jobs with Justice, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - North Carolina, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Greensboro North Carolina, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - North Carolina, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Greensboro, North Carolina, 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Grassroots Leadership (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - North Carolina, 1998-1999 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Cleveland Jobs with Justice, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Columbus Jobs with Justice, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Ohio Database, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - New Hampshire, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Trenton, new jersey, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - New Jersey Jobs with Justice, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - New Jersey, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - New Jersey, 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - New jersey Citizen Action, 1992-1996 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - New Mexico, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Albany, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Albany Jobs with Justice, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Albany Solidarity Committee of the Capitol District, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Long Island, New York, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - New York City Workers' Rights Board, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Jobs with Justice and Religion, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Albany, New York, 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Alabama Jobs with Justice, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Little Rock, Arkansas, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Fayetteville, Arkansas, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Arkansas Jobs with Justice, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Arkansas, 1997-1999 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Arkansas Jobs with Justice, 1995-2000 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Atlanta, Georgia, 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Atlanta, Georgia Labor Council, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Atlanta Georgia Labor Council, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Atlanta, Georgia Labor Council, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Atlanta, Georgia Labor Council, 1992-1993 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Arizona, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Tucson Trip, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 47)
    December 2001
  - SAAEJ, Arizona Jobs with Justice, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Arizona, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Phoenix, Arizona, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - Phoenix, Arizona, 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - Phoenix, Arizona, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - Phoenix Jobs with Justice, 1993-1996 (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - SAAEJ, 2001-2002 (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - Tucson, 2000-2001 (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - Tucson Jobs with Justice, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 56)
  - Tucson, Arizona, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 57)
  - Tucson, Arizona, 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 58)
  - Tucson, Brush Wellman Workers' Rights Board Hearing, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 59)
  - California Interest in Jobs with Justice, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 60)
- E5: Local Coalitions 1992-2003 (Box 21)
  - Fresno Labor, Community Alliance Newsletter, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Fresno Jobs with Justice, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Maritime Trade Workers, Fresno, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Fresno, California, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Orange County, California Workers for Justice and Democracy, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - San Diego Jobs with Justice, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - South Bay, California (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Colorado, 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Colorado, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Colorado Workers' Rights Board, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Fresno Jobs with Justice, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Colorado Planning Retreat, 1996-1997 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Colorado Jobs with Justice, 1996-1999 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Colorado Jobs with Justice, 1995-1998 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Colorado Jobs with Justice, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Colorado Jobs with Justice, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Colorado Workers' Rights Board, 1998-1999 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Englewood, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Denver, Workers' Rights Board, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Englewood, Colorado, 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Colorado Jobs with Justice Newsletter, 1995-1996 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Colorado Jobs with Justice Workers' Rights Board (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Connecticut, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Washington, DC, Local Jobs with Justice, 1994-2001 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Labor Publications, 2001-2003 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Miami, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Miami, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Miami, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Miami Jobs with Justice, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Miami, 1999-2000 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Miami Planning Retreat, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Miami, Living wage and Background Jobs with Justice, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Atlanta, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Atlanta, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Atlanta, Georgia Jobs with Justice, 1999-2000 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Atlanta Labor Council, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Jobs with Justice Committee of the Atlanta Labor Council, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Chicago, 1999-2003 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Chicago, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Chicago, 1998-1999 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Chicago Jobs with Justice, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Chicago Workers' Rights Board, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Chicago Jobs with Justice, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Chicago May Day Protests Press Clips, other 2000 Actions and Materials (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Chicago, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Chicago Workers' Rights Board and Jobs with Justice, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Chicago, Illinois, 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Chicago Workers' Rights Board, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Indianapolis, 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - Bloomington, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - Bloomington, Indiana, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - Bloomington Jobs with Justice, 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - Bloomington Jobs with Justice, 1992-2000 (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - Bloomington, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 54)
  - Indianapolis Jobs with Justice, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 55)
  - Indianapolis Jobs with Justice, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 56)
  - Bloomington Jobs with Justice, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 57)
  - Calumet Project for Industrial Jobs, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 58)
  - Indiana, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 59)
  - St. Joseph Valley Project, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 60)
  - St. Joseph, South Bend, 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 61)
  - Iowa, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 62)
- E6: Local Coalitions 1992-2003 (Box 22)
  - Wisconsin Jobs with Justice, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 1997-1998 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Milwaukee Workers' Rights Board, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Milwaukee, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Campaign for Sustainable Milwaukee, 1995-1997 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Milwaukee Solidarity Committee, Jobs with Justice, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - West Virginia, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Detroit Jobs with Justice, 1997-2003 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Central Florida Jobs with Justice, 2009 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - North Carolina Triad Jobs with Justice, 2009 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Tri-State, Evansville, Charter Application, 2011 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - North Texas, 1991-2003 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - North Texas Jobs with Justice, 1994-1996 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - North Texas Jobs with Justice, 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - North Texas Jobs with Justice Update, 1998-2000 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - North Texas Jobs with Justice Workers' Rights Board, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - San Antonio, Texas, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - San Antonio, Texas, 1997-1998 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - The Center for Campus Organizing, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Austin, Texas, 1997-1998 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Dallas Jobs with Justice, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Dallas, Texas, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Dallas, Texas, 1997-1998 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Knoxville, Tennessee, 1997-1998 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Nashville, Tennessee, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Nashville, 1998-1999 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Middle Tennessee Jobs with Justice Nashville, 1995-1998 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Nashville, Tennessee, 1997-1998 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Tennessee, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Dallas, 2002-2003 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Dallas Jobs with Justice, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Middle Tennessee, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Nashville 2001 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - South Dakota, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Tennessee Jobs with Justice, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Knoxville, Tennessee Jobs with Justice, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Knoxville, Tennessee, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Washington State, 2002-2003 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Washington State Jobs with Justice, 2001-2002 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Seattle, Washington, 1997-1998 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Washington State Jobs with Justice, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Rhode Island, 2002-2003 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Pittsburgh, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Philadelphia Jobs with Justice, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Philadelphia, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - Philadelphia, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - Philadelphia, 2002-2003 (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - Philadelphia, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - Philadelphia, 1999-2002 (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - Pittsburgh, 2002-2003 (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - Pittsburgh, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - Pittsburgh, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - APA Pittsburgh, 1998-1999 (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1997-1998 (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - Alliance for Progressive Action Update, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 55)
  - Pittsburgh, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 56)
  - Pennsylvania Jobs with Justice, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 57)
  - Pennsylvania Jobs with Justice, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 58)
  - Miscellaneous, 2002-2003 (Box 22, Folder 59)
- E7: Local Coalitions 1992-2003 National Coalitions and Campaigns (Box 23)
  - Utah, 2002-2003 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Utah, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Salt Lake City, Utah Jobs with Justice, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - North Virginia, 1999-2000 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Vermont, 2002-2003 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Vermont Jobs with Justice, 1992-2002 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - IBT, Teamster Magazine, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Mid-Willamette Jobs with Justice, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Mid-Willamette, Oregon, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Portland, Oregon Direct Action and JWJ, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Salem, Oregon, 1997-1998 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Portland, Oregon, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Portland Jobs with Justice, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Washington Jobs with Justice, 1999-2001 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Portland, Oregon, 1997-1998 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Portland, Oregon Jobs with Justice, 1994-1996 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    Contians 2 floppy discs
  - Washington State Jobs with Justice, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Washington State Jobs with Justice, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Washington State Jobs with Justice, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Alaska, 1993-1994 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Washington State Jobs with Justice, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Washington State Labor Council, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Seattle, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Washington State Jobs with Justice, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Portland Jobs with Justice, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - ESSN, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Tide Water, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Tidewater, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - ESSN, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - ESSN, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - ESSN, Jobs with Justice, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - ESSN, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Portland Jobs with Justice, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Eugene, Oregon, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Eugene, Oregon, 1997-1998 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Eugene, Oregon Solidarity Network, 1991-1998 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Eugene Oregon Solidarity Network Newsletter, 1993-1996 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - ACTWU, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - "50 Years is Enough", 2000 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Acorn Living Wage Campaign, 1995-1997 (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Black Workers for Justice, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Campaign for an America that Works, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Books and Jobs and Economics, 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Welfare Reform and Community Change, 1997-1999 (Box 23, Folder 44)
- E8: National Coalitions and Campaigns (Box 24)
  - Center for Community Change, 2000-2001 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Center for Community Change, Jobs Creation, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Driver's License Campaigns, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Gray Panthers, 1997-1998 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Grass Roots Intuitive Policy Project (GRIPP), 2000 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Grassroots Leadership, Community Assets Campaign, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Immigrants Rights Legislation, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Institute for democratic Renewal and Project Change Anti-Racism Initiative (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Institute for Policy Studies, 1996-2000 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - IPS, Letelier Moffit Award, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Highlander Research and Education Center, Highlander Reports, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Institute for Policy Studies, Progressive Challenge, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Interfaith Center on Corporate Responsibility (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - International Human Rights Law Group, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - International Mission Church, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Jewish Fund for Justice (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - JEDI for Women (Justice, Economic Dignity and Independence), 1998 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Jews United for Justice, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - International Conference of Free Trade Unions, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Immigrant Organizing, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Institute for America's Future, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Labor History Tour Bus, Harmonicas Hinds Contracts, Chicago Annual Meeting, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Workers' Rights Board in Congressional Record, Chicago Annual Meeting, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 23)